worldstart.com 2003-06-22

# WorldStart

**Privacy Policy**  

Your privacy is important to us. Since we have offer a number of different services here at WorldStart, we've divided our privacy policy into several parts; General Policies, Software Purchases, Newsletters, and the Computer Tips Message Board. 

**General Policies  
****  
**

We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. 

You can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data.   

We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations.

**Software Purchases  
****  
**

All information submitted to us during the course of a software purchase is kept strictly confidential, regardless of the method of purchase (i.e. credit card, PayPal, phone, mail).

We do not disclose your information to outside marketers or advertisers.

We do use cookies in conjunction with our shopping cart and affiliate program in order to keep track of the items you wish to purchase. This information is kept strictly confidential.

Our shopping cart system will remember your information for future purchases and this information is kept strictly confidential as well.

**Newsletters  
****  
**

We only collect e-mail addresses for our newsletters and we do not attempt to identify any individual on our list.

Subscriber e-mail addresses are kept strictly confidential. They are not disclosed to outside marketers and are only used to send you the newsletters you sign up for - nothing more.

Information sent to us via e-mail may be used in one or more of our newsletters at our discretion. This includes computer questions, tips, jokes, reader's stories, and other relevant newsletter content. We will not post any information in our newsletters that contains personal information (with the exception of a first name for newsletter content) unless specifically asked to do so. 

Non-newsletter related inquires and e-mails are kept strictly confidential.

**Computer Tips Message Board  
****  
**  
We do not harvest names or e-mail addresses from our Computer Tips Message Board (hereafter CTMB). We may, from time to time, use one of the questions asked in our Computer Tips Newsletter, but we will not disclose the name, e-mail, or any other information about the writer.

Since the CTMB is a public forum, we can not guarantee that other users will not take the information you post there (i.e. name, e-mail, etc).

**Contact Information  
******

Should you have any questions on our privacy policy, feel free to contact us at the e-mail address below:

|    
---|---  
  |    
  
**Great Deals Just For You!  
****  
**
